{"data":[{"question":"___ is a five-cent coin in America.","a":"A nickel","b":"Nickel","c":"Nickels","d":"The Nickel","answer":"1","explain":"\n - A nikel = One Nickel ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"There are four _________ in our class.","a":"Mary","b":"Maries","c":"Mary's","d":"Marys","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Four Marys = four girls named Mary","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Where are the ___ magazines ?","a":"women's","b":"women","c":"womens","d":"woman","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n-We often say  \"Women's magazines\" to express \"magazine for women\" ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"His house is within ___ from the post office.","a":"stone's throw","b":"a throw of a stone","c":"a stone's throw","d":"the stone's throw","answer":"3","explain":"\n-A stone's throw from something\/away (from something)NEAR very close to something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I saw ___ at the barber's.","a":"my sister's a boy friend","b":"a boy friend of my sister","c":"boy friend of my sister","d":"my sister boy friend","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A boy friend of my sister: one of my sister's friend","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Who are those boys? \" Those boys are friends of ___.","a":"them","b":"they","c":"their","d":"theirs","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Theirs= their friends","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"___ twelve can be divided by 2 , 3 , 4 and six.","a":"Number","b":"A number","c":"The number","d":"Numbers","answer":"2","explain":"\n-\"A\" and \"an\" signal that the noun modified is indefinite, referring to any member of a group \n- Any \"twelve (12) has the same characteristics (divide by 1,3...)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher advised Jane to read the passage at the end of ____.","a":"chapter seven","b":"the seven chapter","c":"seventh chapter","d":"chapter the seventh","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- We often say: chapter 1, chapter 2... \n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"When I got to the theater, they were already playing ___.","a":"second act","b":"the act two","c":"act two","d":"the act second","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- We often say: act 1, act 2... ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you happen to know ___ insulin is?","a":"what kind of a substance","b":"what kind of substance","c":"what kind a substance","d":"of what kind of substance","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We do not use article to talk about things in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}